<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Credo Action's Feed</title><link>http://credoaction.com/news/home.html</link><description>This is a test feed base on the Credo Action email newsletter</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 00:51:57 GMT</pubDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Tell the Justice Department: Investigate apparent FBI spying on Wal-Mart employees</title><link>http://act.credoaction.com/sign/FBI_walmart?t=1&amp;akid=16568.6999848.B3Y6-9</link><description>Tell the Justice Department: Investigate reported FBI spying on Wal-Mart employees. We need to make sure the Justice Department doesn’t turn a blind eye any outrageous and dangerous abuse of authority targeting Wal-Mart workers. So why is the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) Terrorism Task Force reportedly teaming up with Walmart to spy on employees? So we are joining our friends at OUR Walmart to demand that the Department of Justice investigate the FBI’s relationship with Wal-Mart and whether the agency or company broke any laws. According to a recent front-page article in Bloomberg Magazine, Wal-Mart hired a defense contractor, Lockheed Martin, to use military-grade cybersecurity techniques to monitor the social media accounts of labor organizers and Wal-Mart employees.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">http://act.credoaction.com/sign/FBI_walmart?t=1&amp;akid=16568.6999848.B3Y6-9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 00:51:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CREDO Action Home</title><link>http://credoaction.com/?akid=16568.6999848.B3Y6-9&amp;rd=1&amp;t=8</link><description>In conflict zones around the globe, where rape is often used as a tool of control and where women’s and girls’ bodies are often a battleground, the Helms Amendment has been wielded to block women who have been raped from accessing abortions in their most urgent time of need. But it doesn’t have to be this way.  Without waiting for Congress, President Obama can issue an executive order clarifying Helms.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">http://credoaction.com/?akid=16568.6999848.B3Y6-9&amp;rd=1&amp;t=8</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 00:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Walmart Keeps an Eye on Its Massive Workforce</title><link>http://www.bloomberg.com/features/2015-walmart-union-surveillance/</link><description>The billions in sales typical of a Walmart Black Friday were threatened. The one formed that September included representatives from global security, labor relations, and media relations. The labor relations team reported “a record-breaking” 1,600 hotline calls from 977 stores; 250 locations reported protests of some kind. Walmart also won seven statewide court injunctions preventing the UFCW and anyone else who wasn’t an employee from protesting on Walmart property. OUR Walmart maintains that about 400 Walmart employees went on strike and that they or their supporters took action at almost 1,200 stores around the country.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.bloomberg.com/features/2015-walmart-union-surveillance/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 00:51:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Organization United for Respect at Walmart</title><link>http://www.united4respect.org/doj</link><description>Download letters to the Department of Justice from OUR Walmart members in response to reported FBI coordination with Walmart to track and surveil Walmart workers standing up for respect and fair pay at Walmart. Click here to read the letter to Principal Deputy Assistant Attorney General Vanita Gupta. 

Click here to read the letter to Principal Deputy Assistant Attorney General, Civil Division, Benjamin Mizer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.united4respect.org/doj</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 00:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. labor board alleges Wal-Mart violated labor law in 14 states</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-walmart-labor-idUSBREA0E1PY20140115#zkszLVDLKDCyr1Qd.97</link><description>The next step is for an NLRB administrative law judge to oversee a trial to determine whether Wal-Mart broke the law. A complaint issued by the NLRB's general counsel's office said Wal-Mart representatives appeared on national news broadcasts and threatened to retaliate against workers if they went on strike. Dozens of employees received verbal and written warnings, formal reprimands and were otherwise disciplined after striking last year for improved wages and working conditions at Wal-Mart stores, according to the complaint. A man chants outside Wal-Mart during a protest for better wages and working conditions during Black Friday in San Leandro, California November 29, 2013. In the Wal-Mart case, a preliminary investigation by the NLRB revealed that charges against the retailer likely had merit.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.reuters.com/article/us-walmart-labor-idUSBREA0E1PY20140115#zkszLVDLKDCyr1Qd.97</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 00:51:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Organization United for Respect at Walmart</title><link>http://www.united4respect.org/doj</link><description>Download letters to the Department of Justice from OUR Walmart members in response to reported FBI coordination with Walmart to track and surveil Walmart workers standing up for respect and fair pay at Walmart. Click here to read the letter to Principal Deputy Assistant Attorney General Vanita Gupta. 

Click here to read the letter to Principal Deputy Assistant Attorney General, Civil Division, Benjamin Mizer.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.united4respect.org/doj</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 00:51:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>